name: 'Common Verbs 3'
questions:
  -
    question: 'Call me when you $ the airport.'
    answers:
      - 'arrive at'
      - 'arrive in'
      - 'arrive on'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'If you fall from a bike you can $ your leg.'
    answers:
      - change
      - lose
      - break
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I want to $ a ticket to see my favorite movie, but it''s too expensive.'
    answers:
      - pay
      - rent
      - buy
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'People usually don''t want to $ from their vacation.'
    answers:
      - come
      - 'come back'
      - go
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I can''t $ a job. Can you help me?'
    answers:
      - seek
      - look
      - find
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I started to $ a new language - French. It''s very hard.'
    answers:
      - teach
      - say
      - learn
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Can you $ my friend at the airport tomorrow?'
    answers:
      - meet
      - see
      - find
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'You can $ a car if you don''t have it.'
    answers:
      - pay
      - rent
      - hire
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'He always $ hello to people at work.'
    answers:
      - speaks
      - tells
      - says
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'We want to $ at a hotel for a night in New York.'
    answers:
      - stand
      - stay
      - stop
    correct: 2
